http://www.atlanticlifts.com/privacy-policy/

Atlantic Lifts Ltd. respects your privacy
Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of Atlantic Lifts Ltd.
Credit card details
Atlantic Lifts Ltd. will never ask for Credit Card details and request that you do not enter it on any of the forms on Atlantic Lifts Ltd.
External Sites
Atlantic Lifts Ltd. is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.
Cookies
A “cookie” is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows Atlantic Lifts Ltd. to recognize you each time you visit this site(customization etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and Atlantic Lifts Ltd. does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as newsfeeds.
Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The Internet
While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to Atlantic Lifts Ltd. and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through Atlantic Lifts Ltd. have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.
